Guide to the ILR School Communications Department Publications 1996-2018
ILR School Communications Department Publications
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
ILR School Communications Department Publications, 1996-2018
/4264 PUBS
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR); Communications Department
3.3 linear ft.
Publications (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
ILR School Communications Department Publications including ILR catalogs and workshop literature
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Communications Department
Form and Genre Terms:
Publications (documents).
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
/4264: ILR School Communications Department Director's Files
/4264 P: ILR School Communications Department Photographs
CONTAINER LIST
- ILR Communications Department Publications, 2000-2004 (Box 1)
  - Management Development Workshops, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Management Development Workshops in Rochester, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
      By ILR School Cornell. Item is in English.
  - Champions and Work, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Champions @ Work: Employment, Workplace Practices and Labor- Management Relations in Western New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By ILR School Cornell University. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Champions @ Work: Employment, Workplace Practices and Labor- Management Relations in Western New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By ILR School Cornell University. Copy 1. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Champions @ Work: Employment, Workplace Practices and Labor- Management Relations in Western New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By ILR School Cornell University. Copy 2. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Champion @ Work: Employment, Workplace Practices and Labor-Management relations ni Western New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      By Western Region of Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Spiral notebook slightly damaged. Item is in English.
  - ILR Catalog, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Fall
    - Item 1: Workshops & Programs Fall 2000, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Workshops & Programs Fall 2000, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Copy 1. Item is in English.
  - Workshop Brochures, 2000-2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Cornell University New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations: Advancing the World of Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      By Cornell University New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Cornell University New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations: Advancing the World of Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      By Cornell University New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Copy 1. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Cornell University New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations: Advancing the World of Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      By Cornell University New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - ILR Catalog, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Spring
    - Item 1: Workshops & Programs Spring 2001, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - General Workshops, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Item 2: Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Item 3: Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Copy 2. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations: Labor Relations Management Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      By Cornell Univeristy School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations: Labor Relations Management Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Human Resources Workshops, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations: Human Resources Program - Ithaca and Other Cities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 2: Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations: Human Resources Program - Ithaca and Other Cities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 3: Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations: Human Resources Program - Ithaca and Other Cities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Management Workshops, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations: Management Development Workshops on Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Item 2: Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations: Management Development Workshops on Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Labor Relations Certificate Workshops, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Spring/Fall
    - Item 1: Labor Relations Certificate Programs Management Series, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial Labor and Relations. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Labor Relations Certificate Programs Management Series, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial Labor and Relations. Copy 1. Item is in English.
  - Advance Your Career, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Advancing the World of Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Item 2: Advancing the World of Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Item 3: Advancing the World of Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ILR Catalog, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 2001, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Item 2: Cornell University ILR: Advancing the World of Work, Workshops & Programs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial Labor Relations. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Cornell University ILR: Advancing the World of Work, Workshops & Programs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial Labor Relations. Copy 1. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Cornell University ILR: Advancing the World of Work, Workshops & Programs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial Labor Relations. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Information Packet, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Advancing the World of Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial Labor and Relations. Folder filled with pamphlets. Item is in English.
  - Workshops, 2001-2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Supervisory Studies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 2: Buffalo Labor Studies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 3: EEO Certificate Programs and Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 4: eCornell: Win Year of free Online Certificate Course in Human Resources from eCornell, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 5: ILR Cornell University, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 6: ILR Cornell University, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 7: ILR Cornell University, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 8: ILR Cornell University, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 9: eCornell, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 10: ILR Cornell University, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 11: Cornell University ILR: Labor Relations Management Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Item 12: eCornell: Win a Year of Free Online Certificate Courses in Human Resources from eCornell, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
      By eCornell. Copy 1. Item is in English.
    - Item 13: eCornell, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - ILR Catalog, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Cornell University, ILR: Workshops & Programs Spring 2002, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Item 2: Cornell ILR: Workshops & Programs Spring 2002, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Item 3: Cornell ILR: Workshops & Programs Spring 2002, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - General Workshops, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Cornell University, ILR: 2002 Spring Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 2: Delivering Competitive adavntage through Human Resource Systems, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 3: Cornell University, ILR: 2002 Spring Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 4: Spring 2002 Rochester Workshops at Cornell University, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 5: Cornell University, ILR: 2002 Spring Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 6: Cornell University, ILR: 2002 Spring Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 7: Cornell University, ILR: Spring 2002 Workshops & Programs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 8: Cornell University, ILR: 2002 Spring Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 9: Cornell University, ILR: 2002 Spring Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 10: Leadership Skills, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations Rochester District. Item is in English.
    - Item 11: Spring 2002 Rochester Workshops at Cornell University, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 12: Cornell University, ILR: 2002 Spring Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 13: Cornell University, ILR: 2002 Spring Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 14: Cornell University, ILR: 2002 Spring Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 15: Cornell University, ILR: Spring 2002 Workshops & Programs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 16: Cornell University, ILR: Spring 2002 Workshops & Programs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Item 17: Cornell University, ILR: Spring 2002 Workshops & Programs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - ILR Catalog, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Summer
    - Item 1: Advancing the World of Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Item 2: Advancing the World of Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - General Workshops, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Human Resources Workshops in Ithaca, N.Y., Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 2: Human Resources Workshops in Ithaca, N.Y., Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 3: Workshops in Ithaca, N.Y., Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 4: Human Resources Workshops in Ithaca, N.Y., Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 5: Management Workshops in Ithaca, N.Y., Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Item 6: Management Workshops in Ithaca, N.Y., Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - ILR Catalog, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Advancing the World of Work: Fall 2002 Catalog, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Item 2: Advancing the World of Work: Fall 2002 Catalog, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Item 3: Advancing the World of Work: Fall 2002 Catalog, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - General Workshops, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Professional Development Workshops & Certificates in Labor Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Item 2: Professional Development Workshops & Certificates in Labor Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Item 3: Professional Development Workshops & Certificates in Labor Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Item 4: Management Development Workshops in Ithaca, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Item 5: Fall 2002: Human Resource, Management Development, and Labor Relations Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Item 6: Supervising for Success, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Labor Relations Workshops, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Labor Relations Management Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Item 2: Labor Relations Management Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Item 3: Labor Relations Management Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Management Workshops, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Management Offerings Winter 2002, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations Albany Extension. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Labor Relations Certificate Programs in Western New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations Western Region. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Management Workshops in Ithaca, N.Y., Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - IWS Briefings, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Institute for Workplace Studies Briefing, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 2: Institute for Workplace Studies Briefing, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Item 3: Institute for Workplace Studies Briefing, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - ILR Catalog, 2002-2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Advancing the World of Work: Professional Development, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 2: Advancing the World of Work: Professional Development, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Item 3: Advancing the World of Work: Professional Development, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Human Resources Workshops, 2002-2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Human Resources Professional Development Workshops in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 2: Human Resources Professional Development Workshops in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Item 3: Human Resources Professional Development Workshops in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Management Development Workshops, 2002-2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Management Development Workshops in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Item 2: Management Development Workshops in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Item 3: Management Development Workshops in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Alternative Dispute Resolution Studies, 2002-2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Alternative Dispute Resolution Studies Advancing the World of Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Item 2: Alternative Dispute Resolution Studies Advancing the World of Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies, 2002-2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Buffalo Labor Studies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Item 2: Buffalo Labor Studies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - ILR Catalog, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Advancing the World of Work: Professional Development Workshops & Certificates, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 2: Advancing the World of Work: Professional Development Workshops & Certificates, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Item 3: Advancing the World of Work: Professional Development Workshops & Certificates, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - General Workshops, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: Management Development and Human Resources Professional Development Workshops in Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 2: Management Development and Human Resources Professional Development Workshops in Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 3: Management Development and Human Resources Professional Development Workshops in Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 4: Management Development and Human Resources Professional Development Workshops in Albany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 5: Management Development and Human Resources Professional Development Workshops in Albany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 6: Leadership Skills, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Item 7: Leadership Skills, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - ILR Catalog, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Spring/Summer
    - Item 1: Professional Development Workshops & Certificates, Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Item 2: Professional Development Workshops & Certificates, Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - General Workshops, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: Management Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 2: Management Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 3: Management Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 4: Labor Relations Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 5: Labor Relations Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 6: Human Resources Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Long Island, and Ithaca, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 7: Human Resources Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Long Island, and Ithaca, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 8: Diversity and Equal Employment OpportunitiesProfessional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 9: Diversity and Equal Employment Opportunities Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Item 10: Diversity and Equal Employment Opportunities Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - General Workshops, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: Workshops held at Cornell in Ithaca, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Item 2: Workshops held at Cornell in Ithaca, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Item 4: Summer 2003 Workshops in Ithaca, NY, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Item 5: Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Item 6: Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Item 7: Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial Labor and Relations. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - General Workshops, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: Management Development and Human Resources Professional Development Workshops held in Albany, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 2: Management Development and Human Resources Professional Development Workshops held in Albany, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 3: Management Development and Human Resources Professional Development Workshops held in Albany, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 4: Emotional Intelligence in the Workplace, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 5: Emotional Intelligence in the Workplace, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 6: Emotional Intelligence in the Workplace, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 7: Emotional Intelligence in the Workplace, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 8: Professional Development Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 9: Professional Development Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 10: Professional Development Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 11: Cornell Universitys Professional Development Workshops held in Long, Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 12: Cornell Universitys Professional Development Workshops held in Long Island, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Item 13: Cornell Universitys Professional Development Workshops held in Long Island, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Rochester Workshops, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Winter/Spring
    - Item 1: Winter & Spring 2003 Schedule, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - A Tribute to Auto Workers, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: A Tribute to Auto Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Item 2: A Tribute to Auto Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - IWS Briefing, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: Institute for Workplace Studies Briefing, Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Item 2: Institute for Workplace Studies Briefing, Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Certificate Workshops, 2003-2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: New York City Labor Studies Credit Certificate Program and Union Leadership Workshop Series, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Item 2: Advanced Human Resources Studies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Item 3: Advanced Human Resources Studies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Item 4: Advanced Human Resources Studies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Professional Development Workshops, 2003-2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: Management Development Workshops held in New York City and Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 2: Management Development Workshops held in New York City and Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 3: Management Development Workshops held in New York City and Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 4: Human Resources Professional Development Workshops held in New York City and Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 5: Human Resources Professional Development Workshops held in New York City and Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 6: Human Resources Professional Development Workshops held in New York City and Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 7: Labor Relations Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 8: Labor Relations Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 9: Labor Relations Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 10: Diversity and EEO Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 11: Diversity and EEO Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Item 12: Diversity and EEO Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Skills Workshops, 2003-2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: Efficiency Skills for Success, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Item 2: Efficiency Skills for Success, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Item 3: Efficiency Skills for Success, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Item 4: Training Skills for Success, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Item 5: Training Skills for Success, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Professional Development Workshops and Certificate Catalog, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: Professional Development Workshops and Certificates, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Professional Developments Workshops and Certificate Catalog, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: Professional Development Workshops and Certificates, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Professional Development Workshops and Certificates Catalog, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)